Suffrage Collection, 1851-2009 (bulk 1880s-1920s)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES I. UNITED STATES
  - Individuals
    - Laidlaw, Harriet Brown: photographs, correspondence, and clippings 1922, 1946, 1949, [see also Subjects--Parades for additional photograph] (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Leonard, Gertrude: obituary 1951 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Leslie, Miriam (Mrs. Frank Leslie): photographundated, [see also States--New York--Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission] (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Loines, Mary Hillard: obituary 1949 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - McCormick, Mildred Medill: photographundated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Milholland, Inez (Mrs. Eugene Boissevain): clippings, correspondence, and photograph 1912-18, [see also Subjects--Parades for additional photographs] (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Miller, Alice Duer: photograph and clippingsundated, [see also BOOKS ON SHELF] (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Morris, Esther (the mother of woman suffrage), [see States--Wyoming] (Box 8)
    - Nichols, Clarina Howard: clipping 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Palmer, Rhoda: clipping, n.d., [see also The Woman's Journal17 October 1908, in Periodicals Collection, for photograph] (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Park, Alice: photographs, clipping, reminiscences, articles, speeches, and biographical material compiled by Una Winter, 1912-48, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Park, Maud Wood: photographs andletters 1946-51, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Paul, Alice: clippings andobituary 1939, undated, [see also Subjects--White House picketing; Suffragist Oral History Project: Conversations with Alice Paul; and Miscellaneous Organizations Collection--National Women's Party] (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Rankin Jeannette: photographs and clippings 1917, 1968-72, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Reid, Helen Rodgers (Mrs. Ogden): photographundated, [see also Subjects--Parades for additional photograph] (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Richardson, Grace: typescript history of suffrage in Nebraska, photograph, and correspondence 1960, undated, [see also States--Nebraska] (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Shaw, Anna Howard
      - Clippings and pamphlets, memorial service programs, and ephemera 1897, 1911-19, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Photographsundated (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence 1914-16 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Slade, Carolyn McCormick: photographs and clippings 1951 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Julia Holmes: clippings 1899-1900, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Taylor, Mentia: photographundated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Tiffany, Katrina Brandes Ely: photographundated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Vanderlip, Narcissa Cox (Mrs. Frank A.): photographsundated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Weed, Helena Hill: clipping and manuscript 1940, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Whitehouse, Vera Boarman: photographs, correspondence, clippings, and programs from New York State Woman Suffrage Association events 1917-19, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Young, Rose: clippings and photographs 1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Younger, Maud: biographical information and article by Younger 1943, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Memorabilia
    - Advertising cards 1910, 1914, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Bluebirds (metal), Massachusetts Woman Suffrage Association, inscribed "Votes for WomenNov. 2," n.d. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Buttons (includes photographs of the Alice Park button collection)undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Canvas bag ("Votes for Women"), [see OVERSIZE MATERIALSand Photographs] (Box 9)
    - Fans (Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and New York), [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 9)
    - Hatchetundated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Pennants ("Votes for Women"), [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS and Photographs] (Box 9)
    - Photographs, slides, and negatives of buttons, pennants, and canvas bagundated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Playing cardsundated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Postcards, Valentines, and greeting cardsundated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Ribbons, "For the Amendment," undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Sewing accessories: hooks and eyes, thimble, and thread holderundated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Songs: suffrage march songs and directions 1915, undated; Suffrage Songs and Verses by Charlotte Perkins Gilman (2 copies), 1911; Sing Out! by Julia Ward Howe, winter 1957; and correspondence with song enclosed, to Alice Park, from Jane Campbell, 1911, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS for phonograph record album: "Songs of the Suffragettes," 1958 (cassette copy in Media Center)] (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Stamps, fiftieth and seventy-fifth anniversary: envelopes with stamps (first day of issue), pamphlet, page of stamps 1915, 1970, 1995, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Stickers (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Veil, "Votes for Women", [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 10)
  - States
    - Multiple states: pamphlets and leaflets 1909-13, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Arizona: leaflets and newsletter (in Spanish) 1912, undated, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Arkansas: pamphlet 1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - California: book, pamphlets, reports, typed reminiscences, and clippings (some material in Spanish, French, and German) 1895, 1907-17, undated, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Colorado; pamphlet, clippings, and typed reminiscences 1877, 1899, 1910-11, 1953, undated, [see also Organizations--NAWSA--Pamphlets] (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut: leaflets, pamphlets, and photographs 1870-71, 1914, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia: pamphlet 1931 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Florida: clipping and pamphlet 1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Georgia: pamphlets 1944, 1958-59 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Idaho: periodical (Idaho Yesterdays) 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Illinois: pamphlets, notes, song lyrics, clippings, and commemorative book 1914-17, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Indiana: leafletsundated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Iowa: pamphlets, leaflet, and clippings 1884, 1969, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kansas
      - Leaflets and periodical 1867, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - The Championship of Woman, booklet of Kansas speeches by George Francis Train 1867 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Kentucky: pamphlet 1884 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Maine: pamphlets, leaflets, and clippings 1895-96, 1903, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Maryland: pamphlet and leafletundated, [see also MICROFORMS-M24 Cullen scrapbooks] (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts
      - Legislative documents 1869-85 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Pamphlets and clippings 1889-1923, 1958, 1975-1979 undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Photographsundated (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Organizations
        - City and town organizations for equal suffrage 1890, 1908, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 11)
        - College Equal Suffrage League of Massachusetts 1901, 1920, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - Massachusetts Men's League for Woman Suffrage 1912 (Box 11, Folder 13)
        - Massachusetts Woman Suffrage Association
          - General: leaflets, pamphlets, photographs,periodicals, and correspondence 1877, 1908-19, [see also Anti-suffrage and Frances Casement Papers] (Box 11, Folder 14)
          - "The Struggle for Political Power: Tactics Used by the Massachusetts Woman's Suffrage Association During Its First Decade 1870-79," student paper by Elizabeth Byrne, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Michigan: leaflet and periodical (The Michigan Suffragist) 1914, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Missouri: pamphlet 1892 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Montana: "The Winning of Woman Suffrage in Montana," graduate thesis by Doris Buck Ward 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Nebraska: letter 1914, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Nevada: clipping, pamphlet, and photograph regarding Anne Martin 1947-48 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - New Jersey: clippings, leaflets, essay, and pamphlets 1867, 1914-16, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - New York
      - Clippings 1881, 1913-18, 1927, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Organizations
        - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission: The Record of the Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission, Inc. 1917-1929 by Rose Young, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - New York State Woman Suffrage Association/Party, Woman Suffrage Party of the City of New York, and Empire State Campaign Committee, [see also Subjects--Parades]
          - Annual reports 1894, 1915-17 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
          - Printed materials 1879-85, 1912-17, undated (Box 12, Folder 5-7)
          - Suffrage Correspondence School: lessons, exams 1916 (Box 12, Folder 8)
          - Election materials, including correspondence, petitions, tabulated results, address lists, and notes 1915-17, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
          - Photographsundated, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 12, Folder 10)
          - Plaster medallion by Alice Morgan Wright[?], for War Service Fund 1917 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        - Non-Partisan Senatorial Committee: campaign against reelection of James W. Wadsworth 1920 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - Saratoga State Woman Suffrage Convention: clippings 1917 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Pamphlets and histories: miscellaneous organizations and general, 1883, 1894 (includes Constitutional convention material) 1915-17, 1920-93 (includes "Working-class and Immigrant Involvement in the New York City Woman's Suffrage Movement," sociology paper by Elinor Lerner, 1980), n.d. (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
    - North Carolina: The Woman Suffrage Movement in North Carolina by A. Elizabeth Taylor 1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - North Dakota: typescript and clipping 1914, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Ohio: correspondence, clippings, pamphlets, and periodical (Headquarters News Bulletin 1895-1920, 1952-64, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Oregon: pamphlet, photograph, and clippings 1900, 1913, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Correspondence, notes, minutes, and photograph 1913-16, 1947, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Pamphlets and clippings 1886, 1872-75, 1912-14 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Photocopies of "Equal Suffrage Page," (news, cartoon, and poetry supplement offered to newspapers)undated, [originals in OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Scrapbook of the Pennsylvania Men's League for Woman Suffrage 1915-1919, [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 13)
    - Rhode Island: leaflets, pamphlets, and periodicals (The Woman Citizen) 1893, 1911-19, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - South Dakota: The Woman Suffrage Movement in South Dakota by Dorinda Riessen Reed 1958 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Tennessee: pamphlet 1916 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Vermont, [see Individuals--Nichols, Clara Howard] (Box 13)
    - Wisconsin: leaflets, periodical, pamphlet, and clipping 1885, 1911, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Wyoming: histories, pamphlets (including anti-suffrage), press release, clippings, and photographs 1895, 1920-23, 1954-79, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Anti-Suffrage
    - Clippings 1895-1917 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Congressional documents 1886, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Memorabilia
      - Cartoons, postcards, and pledgesundated (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Stickers and buttonundated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - National Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage: pamphlets, leaflets, and correspondence 1913-19, undated (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
    - Pamphlets, fliers, and broadsides 1885-1917, undated (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
    - Periodicals, [see Anti-suffrage Review, Anti-suffragist, Remonstrance, Woman Patriot, and Woman's Protest in the Periodicals Collection] (Box 14)
    - Play: "When Women Vote," 1911 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Song: photocopy of "The Anti-suffrage Rose" sheet music 1915, [original in OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - States
      - Illinois: leaflets, pamphlets, and reports 1906-13 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Maine: pamphlet, n.d (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Massachusetts, [see also Why Women Do Not Want the Ballot]
        - Miscellaneous organizations and general: leaflets, pamphlets, and books 1917, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
        - Legislative Committee on Woman Suffrage (municipal suffrage): pamphlets 1884-98 (Box 14, Folder 14)
        - Massachusetts Association Opposed to the (Further) Extension of Suffrage to Women: annual reports and pamphlets 1894-1914 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
        - Women's Anti-suffrage Association of Massachusetts: pamphlets, leaflets, and clippings 1915-19, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Montana: periodical (National Forum) and leaflet 1909, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Nebraska: leaflets, periodical, and pamphlets 1914, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - New Jersey: pamphlets and leaflets 1914-15, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - New York, [see also Why Women Do Not Want the Ballot]
        - Pamphlets: miscellaneous organizations and general 1894-99, 1905, 1913-17, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - New York State Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage: pamphlets 1894-1916, undated (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
      - Oregon: pamphlets 1906 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Texas, Vermont, and Virginia: pamphlets 1915, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Why Woman Do Not Want the Ballot (5 bound volumes) (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
- SERIES II. ENGLAND
  - Subjects
    - History
      - General: pamphlets, articles, and books 1892-1906, 1955-68, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Fiftieth anniversary: clippings, correspondence, and postage stamps 1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Prisoners
      - General: photograph, pamphlets, and articlescirca 1912-13, 1961, undated, [see also Prisons and Prisoners in Printed materials--Books, below] (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - "Cat and Mouse Act": flier, clippings 1913, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Printed materials
    - Books, [see also BOOKS ON SHELF]
      - The Suffragette by E. Sylvia Pankhurst (signed copy) 1911 (Box 17)
      - Prisons and Prisoners by Lady Constance Lytton 1914 (Box 17)
    - Cartoons, postcards, and humorundated (Box 17, Folder 7)
      [see also Carrie Chapman Catt papers]
    - Clippings (includes anti-suffrage material) 1886-1927, 1957, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Drama: Press Cuttings by George Bernard Shaw, Alice in Ganderland, and Lady Geraldine's Speech 1913, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets (alphabetical by author)circa 1851-1914, undated (Box 18, Folder 1A-8)
    - Anti-suffrage pamphlets 1889, 1907-13 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Poetryundated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Programs from demonstrations and parades 1910, 1913, 1926, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS--ENGLAND--Paper napkin program] (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - "Women in Revolt: the fight for emancipation," contemporary documents on the suffrage movement in England, compiled by Judith Kazantzis1968, [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Organizations
    - British Dominions Women Citizen's Union/ British Dominions Woman Suffrage Union: reports 1916, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Catholic Women's Suffrage Society, [see St. Joan's Alliance] (Box 19)
    - Central Society for Women's Suffrage: reports and pamphlets 1892, 1902-07 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Church League for Woman Suffrage: pamphlets 1909-1914, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Conservative & Unionist Women's Franchise Association: pamphlets 1910-13, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Independent Women's Social & Political Union: periodical (The Independent Suffragette)October 1916 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - International Woman's Suffrage Alliance: flierundated, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Men's League for Women's Suffrage: handbook and pamphletsundated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Men's Political Union for Women's Enfranchisement: pamphlet 1910 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - National Society for Women's Suffrage: pamphlets 1872, 1879, 1890-94 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - National Union of Women's Suffrage Societies
      - General: calendars, pamphlets, and fliers 1898, 1905-19, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Women's Suffrage Pilgrimage (June 18-July 261913 ): photocopies of materials owned by Lisa Unger Baskin, [see also MICROFORMS]
        - Speech and report of events 1913 (Box 19, Folder 14)
        - Caravan journal, route map, and broadsides 1913 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - New Constitutional Society for Women's Suffrage: pamphletundated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Northern Men's Federation for Women's Suffrage: pamphletundated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - St. Joan's Alliance (formerly Catholic Women's Suffrage Society): fliers, pamphlets, periodical, and reports 1912, 1937-45, 1961-64, 1976, 1980, [see also The Catholic Citizen in Periodicals] (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Suffragette Fellowship: pamphlets, fliers, and newsletters 1932-45, undated, [see also Calling All Women in Periodicals Collection] (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Suffragettes of the WSPU: periodical (Suffragette News Sheet )November 1916 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Votes for Women Fellowship: record card and fliers 1914, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Women's Franchise League: report 1899 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Women's Freedom League: pamphlets and reports 1912, 1923-29, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Women's Social and Political Union: pamphlets and fliers 1909-14, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Workers Suffrage Federation: periodical (The Woman's Dreadnought) 1916 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Individuals
    - Barry, Florence: biographical pamphletcirca 1967 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Boyle, Nina: biographical pamphletundated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Fawcett, Millicent Garrett: correspondence, drawings, photographs, clippings, and program 1892-1929, n.d, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - How-Martyn, Edith: obituary and funeral material 1984[?] (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Kenney, Annie: biographical pamphlet and articleundated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Marsh, Charlotte: "Memories" pamphlet 1961 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Newsome, Stella: correspondence and periodical 1956-69, [see also photograph in Individuals--Pankhurst family] (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Pankhurst family, [see also Subjects--Prisoners, and Printed materials--Books]
      - Adela [See Walsh, Adela Pankhurst] (Box 20)
      - Christabel: clippings, pamphlets, and photographs 1905-66, undated (Box 20, Folder 19-20)
      - Emmeline: clippings, telegrams, pamphlets, photographs, and postcards 1909-26, 1950, undated (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - Sylvia: clippings and obituaries 1911-25, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Pethick-Lawrence, Emmeline and Frederick: photographs, invitation, correspondence, pamphlet, and calendar 1909, 1919, 1939-61, [see also Subjects--Prisoners and OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Prelooker, Jaakoff: clippings and brochures 1935, 1946, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Strachey, Rachel Conn: pamphlet 1940 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Walsh, Adela Pankhurst: obituary 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Memorabilia and photographs
    - Photographs 1911, 1951, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Posters, [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 21)
    - Songsundated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Historical reproductions from London Museum's Suffrage Collectionundated (Box 21, Folder 10)
- SERIES III. INTERNATIONAL
  - International women's suffrage: general clippings and printed material 1906-1971, undated, [see also BOOKS ON SHELF] (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Australia: printed material, photograph, and clippings 1902-15, 1967, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Belgium: clipping 1925 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Canada: pamphlets and clippings 1911-29, 1944, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Denmark: photograph of suffragist, Mrs. Johannes Münterundated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - France: pamphlets, correspondence, and clippings (some material in French) 1924-32, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Germany: pamphlet and newsletter (some material in German)undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - India: pamphlets, clippings, and reports 1932-35, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Ireland: pamphlets 1906, 1916, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Japan: clippings about suffrage leader, Fusaye Ichikawa 1928, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - New Zealand: pamphlets and clippings 1902, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Norway: pamphlet 1913 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Philippines: clippings and pamphlets 1937-60 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Scotland: pamphlets 1899, 1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Switzerland: clippings 1957-60 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Syria: correspondence 1949 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Tunisia: clipping 1957 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - UNITED STATES
    - States: Pennsylvania Men's League for Woman Suffrage: scrapbook 1915-1919, [Original: use photocopy in Box 22a] (Box 22)
    - States: Pennsylvania Men's League for Woman Suffrage: scrapbook1915-1919, [Photocopy for research use] (Box 22a)
    - Organizations: National American Woman Suffrage Association: certificate to Susan B. Anthony; "What Breaks up the Home?" 1885, undated (Box 23)
    - Memorabilia
      - Canvas bag ("Votes for Women")undated, [see also Memorabilia--photographs] (Box 23)
      - Fans (3): Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and New Yorkundated (Box 23)
      - "Songs of the Suffragettes": phonograph record album 1958 (Box 23)
    - Individuals: Mary Bartlett Dixon Cullen: scrapbooks (15 volumes) 1909-1920, [Use microfilm copies in Media Center--See MICROFORMS] (Box 24-34)
    - Recovering Our Past: The Struggle for Woman's Suffrage by the Feminist History Research Project: cassette audiotape, slides, and booklet 1974 (Box 35)
  - UNITED STATES
    - Subjects--Parades: pictures, photo, and poster 1917, 1920, undated (Map-case Flat File)
    - Printed materials
      - Clippings, maps and charts 1896-1913 (Map-case Flat File)
      - New York Times31 October 1915 (Map-case Flat File)
      - Suffrage newspapers 1914-17 (Map-case Flat File)
      - San Francisco Sunday Call, Magazine Section, "Women and the Ballot," 4 Jul 1909 (Map-case Flat File)
      - "The Woman Citizen": illustrated cover of The Woman's Journal2 Jun 1917 (Map-case Flat File)
    - States
      - Arizona: El Mensajero (in Spanish) (Map-case Flat File)
      - California: Yellow Ribbon 1906-07 (Map-case Flat File)
      - Iowa: "Under this Banner Strong-Minded Iowa Women Won the Right to Vote," Des Moines Sunday RegisterNov 2, 1969 (Map-case Flat File)
      - Massachusetts: periodicals and programscirca 1914, 1919 (Map-case Flat File)
      - New York: poster 1879; and photograph of the New York State Woman's Suffrage Party at the White House, 1917 (Map-case Flat File)
      - Nebraska: poster for Carrie Chapman Catt speech 1923 (Map-case Flat File)
      - Pennsylvania: Equal Suffrage Pageundated, [please use photocopies in box] (Map-case Flat File)
    - Individuals: "Anna Howard Shaw," Women's Journal 1912; and Phoebe Couzzins, newspaper article, 1826 (Map-case Flat File)
    - Memorabilia
      - Two blue banners, one yellow banner (Map-case Flat File)
      - Pennants (Map-case Flat File)
      - Suffrage veilundated (Map-case Flat File)
    - Anti-suffrage: poster and clippingscirca 1883, 1910; and "Anti-suffrage Rose" sheet music, 1915 (Map-case Flat File)
  - ENGLAND
    - Organizations--International Woman's Suffrage Alliance: flierundated (Map-case Flat File)
    - Individuals--Fawcett, Millicent Garrett: drawings and clipping, n.d (Map-case Flat File)
    - Posters (4): moved from Sanger, including "Cat and Mouse Act," undated and England Suffrage Bill petition poster, n.d. (Map-case Flat File)
    - Paper napkin program 1902 (Map-case Flat File)
    - "Women in Revolt: the fight for emancipation," compiled by Judith Kazantzis 1968 (Map-case Flat File)
- BOOKS ON SHELF
  - A.J.R., Ed., The Suffrage Annual and Women's Who's Who 1913
  - Algeo, Sara M., The Story of a Sub-Pioneer 1925
  - Bernard, Suzanne P., Women in the America Anti-suffrage Movement 1982 (thesis)
  - Björkman, Frances M. and Annie G. Porritt, Woman Suffrage: History, Arguments, Results 1915